

# FABIAN MASSOTTO

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

#### **PROFILE**

I am naturally curious and passionate about technology and innovation, always eager to learn new things and improve my skills. I love working in fast-paced and dynamic environments, with different cultures and backgrounds, where collaboration is key to success. A problem solver at heart, I approach challenging scenarios with a creative mindset and enjoy finding solutions.

#### SKILLS

- Web Development
- DevOps
- Cloud
- o Artificial Intelligence
- Automation
- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- React.js
- Next.js
- Python
- Django
- C#
- SQL
- Azure
- Terraform
- GitHub
- Docker
- Splunk
- Datadog

# **EDUCATION & CERTIFICATIONS**

## **Universidad Tecnológica Nacional**

Electronics Engineer | March 2014 - December 2019

## **Harvard University**

- CS50's: Artificial Intelligence | July ...
- CS50's: Web Programming | January April 2023

## Microsoft

- AI-900: AI Fundamentals | August 2023
- AZ-204: Azure Developer Associate | June 2023
- AZ-900: Azure Fundamentals | December 2020

#### CAREER SUMMARY

#### **ExxonMobil**

Full Stack Developer | Modern Web Development December 2022 - Present

 My role is focused in the design and development of cloud applications, reusable modules and starter kits aimed to improve developer experience across the company.

Software Engineer | Application Performance Engineering April 2022 - December 2022

 My role consisted in the design and development of endto-end, medium to large-scale application performance monitoring solutions, both on premises and in the cloud.

#### Software Engineer | IT Operations Center

July 2020 - April 2022

• My role involved leveraging technology and developing solutions to enhance incident management efficiency.

# **Universidad Tecnológica Nacional**

Assistant Professor | Digital Techniques

March 2020 - Present

 My role is centered around imparting knowledge and fostering the intellectual growth of our students in the fields of: microprocessor architecture, real-time operating systems and embedded system design.

#### **Ernst & Young**

Software Engineer | Computer Forensics

June 2019 - July 2020

 My role has been multifaceted and instrumental in enhancing the efficiency and effectiveness of our investigative processes.

## CONTACT INFO

Country of origin: Argentina Email: massotto.fabian@gmail.com Phone: +54 9 11 3146 2971

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/massottofabian

GitHub: github.com/fabimass